let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1. What is the maximum length of a Python identifier? ?",
    answer: "No fixed length is specified.",
    options: [
      "32",
      "16",
      "128",
      "No fixed length is specified."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2.What will be the output of the following code snippet?print(2*3 + (5 + 6)*(1 + 1))",
    answer:"129",
    options: [
      "129",
      "8",
      "121",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 3.How is a code block indicated in Python??",
    answer: "Indentation",
    options: [
      "Brackets",
      "Indentation",
      "Key",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "4.Which of the following concepts is not a part of Python??",
    answer: "Pointers",
    options: [
      "Pointers",
      "Loops ",
      "Dynamic Typing",
      "All of the above",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "5. Which of the following statements are used in Exception Handling in Python?",
      answer: "all of the above",
      options: [
        "try",
        "except",
        "finally",
        "all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6.Which of the following types of loops are not supported in Python?",
    answer: "none of the above",
    options: [
      "for",
      "while",
      "do-while",
      "none of the above",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "7.Which of the following is the proper syntax to check if a particular element is present in a list?",
  answer: "Both A and B",
  options: [
    "if ele in list",
    "if not ele not in list",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of the above"
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "8.Which of the following functions converts date to corresponding time in Python?",
  answer: "strptime()",
  options: [
    "strptime()",
    "strftime()",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of these"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "9. As what datatype are the *args stored, when passed into a function??",
  answer: "Tupple",
  options: [
    "List",
    "Tupple",
    "Dictionary",
    "None of the above"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "10.As what datatype are the *kwargs stored, when passed into a function?",
  answer: "int a []=new int [4] [];",
  options: [ 
    "List",
    "Tupple",
    "Dictionary",
    "None of the above"
]
},
];